<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>andrew li</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on andrew li</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact 📞</title>
      <link>https://example.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 23:03:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>My inbox is always open!
Whether you have a question or just want to say hi, I&amp;rsquo;ll try my best to get back to you 🤠</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conferences</title>
      <link>https://example.com/conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 23:03:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/conference/</guid>
      <description>2021&amp;nbsp;¶  shinyRGT: A R Shiny app for extraction and visualization of Rat gambling task data, CascadiaRConf, June 4-5, Virtual conference | Video | Slides Accumbal cholinergic interneurons modulate decision making, Society for Neuroscience, Jan 11-13, Virtual conference | Poster Gq stimulation of VTA dopamine neurons enhances addiction vulnerability, Society for Neuroscience, Jan 11-13, Virtual conference | Poster  2020&amp;nbsp;¶  Assessing cue-induced craving in individuals with methamphetamine addiction through portable EEG technology, UBC Psychiatry Virtual research Conference, Oct 15, Virtual Conference | Poster Responding for a conditioned reinforcer does not predict risky decision making in rats, international Behavioural Neuroscience Society, Aug 3, Virtual Conference  2019&amp;nbsp;¶   Investigating the effects of a high-fat, high-sugar diet on risky decision making in rats, UBC Neuroscience Undergraduate Research Conference, Jan 31, Vancouver, BC | Poster</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://example.com/teach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 23:02:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/teach/</guid>
      <description>I am a certified Software Carpentries instructor.
All my teaching materials are freely and publicly available. We created a bookdown textbook to accompany the ECOSCOPE workshops. As well, we created educer, a R package to accompany the workshops.
Upcoming workshops&amp;nbsp;¶  Statistical models in R, Oct 26 &amp;amp; 28 (1-4pm) - sign up here! Introduction to R and RStudio, Nov 16 (2-4pm) - sign up here! Intermediate R programming, Nov 23 &amp;amp; 25 (1-4pm) - sign up here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 23:02:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/publication/</guid>
      <description> 2021&amp;nbsp;¶   shinyJackpot: Visualizing lottery gambling in a large Canadian city, under review.
Andrew Li
PsyArXiv | App | Code | BibTeX
  ECOSCOPE: Data Science Workshops
Kim Dill-Mcfarland, Stephan König, Andrew Li, Gil Henriques, Kris Hong, Yue Liu, Florant Mazel, &amp;amp; Steven Hallam
Online textbook | PDF | Code
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 22:59:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Andrew Li and I am psychology master student at the University of British Columbia, where I am supervised by Jiaying Zhao.
My research focuses on applying psychological principles and insights to address environmental issues. Towards this end, I run field and lab experiments to promote behavior change in waste reduction and climate mitigation.
@drewroc6
@andr3wli
andrewcli.com
andrewc.li@ubc.ca
Google Scholar
Abbreviated CV&amp;nbsp;¶ You can find my full CV hereEducation&amp;nbsp;¶ University of British Columbia</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
